We'll see you there
Hell and Back is a fantasy, comedy, animation film directed by Tom Gianas.
Two best friends set out to rescue their pal after
he's accidentally dragged to hell.
Remy (voice), played by Nick Swardson.
Augie (voice), played by T.J. Miller.
Deema (voice), played by Mila Kunis.
The Devil (voice), played by Bob Odenkirk.
Barb the Angel (voice), played by Susan Sarandon.
Orpheus (voice), played by Danny McBride.
To Hell and Back is a Technicolor and CinemaScope war film released in 1955.
It was directed by Jesse Hibbs and stars Audie Murphy as himself.
It is based on the 1949 autobiography of the same name and is an account of
Murphy's World War II experiences as a soldier in the U.S.
The book was ghostwritten by his friend, David
"Spec" McClure, who served in the U.S.
Army's Signal Corps during World War II.
The film explores themes of tree, hell, carnival, vulgar, stop motion.
The tone is lighthearted.